"It's just the two of them left."
"Someone's here."
"So beautiful!"
"Mu Zixun"
"Nice to meet you all in person."
"Met senior brothers and sisters."
"Hurry, please stand up."
Wait a moment.
"This woman."
"This is the window of the Green Emperor Shield."
"Daughter of Tian Ge Sword Immortal."
"Mu Zi Xun"
"Why hasn't the other person appeared yet?"
"Are you trying to be mysterious?"
"So many spiritual essences."
"I caught it."
"Becoming a sword immortal"
"Watch me as I catch you."
"Overslept."
玉虚峰在这边
"Who are you?"
"My name is Ye Qingyu"
"Elder Nai draws his sword."
"The sword servant arranged for the young master."
"I don't have time to leave first."
"I remember."
Ye Yuqing
"Are you coming or not?"
"Don't come, just go back earlier."
"Here I come, here I come."
"Surely he'll be here soon."
"There's movement."
"On top"
"I'm here."
"Brother Changqing"
"Why are you late?"
"Last night I practiced too much."
"Junior Xu Changqing."
"I've seen a few real people."
"This is Senior Brother and Senior Sister."
"The ceremony has already taken place."
"Come up quickly."
"Brother Changqing"
"Let's go in together."
"So you and Xiao Zixun are siblings, huh?"
"You are also a son of a swordsman."
"Interesting, very interesting."
"Xu Zichuan, the swordsman's son."
"This appearance."
"Sorry, master."
"Passed one night."
Cultivation has improved again.
"Enter the hall."
"This is an extremely mediocre boy."
"What exactly are your capabilities?"
"Please welcome the new disciple."
Please welcome the two of them on stage.
"Pay respects to the Founder of Mount Bai."
"I am Xu Changqing."
"Mù Zǐ Xūn"
"I swear here"
"Eternal Effect Immortal Sect"
"Do not fall into the demonic path."
"For the people."
"Uphold justice"
"From now on, the two of you..."
"I am a disciple of Kunlun."
When you work hard to cultivate yourself
"Protecting the livelihood of all under heaven."
"Cannot be disgraced"
"The name of Kunlun"
"Disciple will remember."
"Is this considered..."
"It's the initiation ceremony."
"Thank you, Master."
"Mysterious golden soft jade armor."
"The Sect Leader is really generous."
"Two people's immortal treasures."
"Except for Senior Brother, no one else is here."
"Today, you have become my disciple."
"I will give this item to you."
"From now on."
"You hold this order."
"From top to bottom of Kunlun"
"As you see me."
"Misty Realm"
"Only the successor of Elder Zhi Jian can wield the Feathered Sabre."
"Is this directly an appointed heir position?"
"This is Xu Changqing's cultivation level."
"Elder Swordsmaster"
"You're treating the future of Kunlun as child's play."
"What's wrong?"
"A wooden sign"
"What's there to argue about?"
"What are you doing?"
"Is this slowing down?"
"This is no child's play."
"Many disciples of Kunlun"
"Everyone's here."
"Could it be Master?"
"Just trust me like that."
"I believe in everlasting youth."
"His talent is not prominent now."
"The way of the heart is steadfast."
| Unlimited potential